<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-10-16T00:13:10+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Aged Carer</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/aged-carer" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aged Carer" /><published>2022-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/aged-carer</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/aged-carer"><![CDATA[<p>When I was living in Japan, my job required me to visit women’s prisons. I worked as a salesman for a company that sells correspondence vocational education packages.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Women prisons in Japan are run only by women. Even the prison guards are women. Female prisoners are deprived of men.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Apparently, there are always a few prisoners who start taking off their clothes whenever they see a man. No matter how ugly he is, it really doesn’t matter. They get so excited about the presence of opposite sex. Taking off their clothes results in a punishment. They have to spend a period of time in an isolation room. They don’t care. They risk it anyway.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>When I visited a jail for the first time, a young woman prisoner took off her clothes as I was walking by her cell. She put her right fist up in her vagina. Before the prison guard had time to get in her cell and beat her up, she managed to have an intense shaking orgasm.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>After that incident, she completed training to be an aged carer before she was released. I think of her whenever I see an aged care center.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was living in Japan, my job required me to visit women’s prisons. I worked as a salesman for a company that sells correspondence vocational education packages.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Caught Red Handed in Japan</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/redhanded-in-japan" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Caught Red Handed in Japan" /><published>2022-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/redhanded-in-japan</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/redhanded-in-japan"><![CDATA[<p>When I went to Japan last time, I got arrested and spent 2 weeks in jail.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I was making graffiti in Shibuya and two police officers came. I was using red spray paint and got literally caught red-handed. I got arrested and put in a detention center. Someone from the Australian embassy visited me in a jail. I was told I have to spend the minimum of 3 months and the maximum of 8 years if I get charged. I was stressed. It would suck to spend that much time in jail.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I was sharing a cell with 2 people, the old and young. The old guy was arrested for tax fraud. He didn’t speak much English at all. He had a photo of his Lamborghini. He looked at the photo all the time. The young one spoke English. He got arrested for robbing a liquor store.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Food was good there. We had miso soup every meal.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I didn’t get charged. I was released after 2 weeks. That was how I got caught red-handed in Japan.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I went to Japan last time, I got arrested and spent 2 weeks in jail.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Car Park</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/car-park" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Car Park" /><published>2022-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/car-park</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/car-park"><![CDATA[<p>While I was snorting coke in the toilet cubicle with Sam, Nick was having a telephone sex in the car park at Eureka community center. It was intermittently drizzling and the air was already cold. The daylight saving time was going to end tomorrow. It was the first Saturday of April. Quang told us that the reason why we use the word dozen for a collection of 12 things was that we used to have twelve fingers. We lost them somehow along the way and the humans collectively decided to forget about them. I had to keep going. There was so much booze and I was so far from home.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I was snorting coke in the toilet cubicle with Sam, Nick was having a telephone sex in the car park at Eureka community center. It was intermittently drizzling and the air was already cold. The daylight saving time was going to end tomorrow. It was the first Saturday of April. Quang told us that the reason why we use the word dozen for a collection of 12 things was that we used to have twelve fingers. We lost them somehow along the way and the humans collectively decided to forget about them. I had to keep going. There was so much booze and I was so far from home.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Body of Water</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/body-of-water" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Body of Water" /><published>2022-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/body-of-water</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/body-of-water"><![CDATA[<p>As I descended, I saw a body of water below.</p>

<p>A log was floating on the water.</p>

<p>One end was burned black and the other was cut clean.</p>

<p>I grabbed the clean end,</p>

<p>and carefully traced the concentric rings one by one with my finger.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>A piece of dirty yellowish brown cloth was floating on the water.</p>

<p>I swam towards the artefact to inspect it,</p>

<p>It was a dead body of a soldier.</p>

<p>My feet touched the sandy bottom and I thought to myself,</p>

<p>the shore is near.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I stood on the land, on the wet sand.</p>

<p>Charcoaled wood pieces, campfire remains,</p>

<p>I walked towards the sand dunes with tiny crabs,</p>

<p>Towards the saltbush shrub before sea level rise and storm surge.</p>

<p>In the twilight of the empire, I saw two red moons in the sky.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I descended, I saw a body of water below.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The origin of pole jumping</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/the-origin-of-pole-jumping" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The origin of pole jumping" /><published>2022-03-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/poll-jumping</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/the-origin-of-pole-jumping"><![CDATA[<p>Pole jumping, also known as pole vaulting, is a competitive sport where the athletes compete against each other on how high they can jump by using a long flexible stick.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>The origin of pole jumping goes way back before humans invented a bridge. Our ancestors used a long stick made out of a tree to boost themselves to jump over rivers. It was an essential survival skill.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>We had to to stop them from crossing the river. They hate water. After all the bridges were destroyed, the only method for us to cross rivers is to use a long flexible stick. You run towards the bank, stick it on the ground, and propel yourself to the other side, just like a pole jumper.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>We have gone back to the way of our ancestors.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pole jumping, also known as pole vaulting, is a competitive sport where the athletes compete against each other on how high they can jump by using a long flexible stick.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Together</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/together" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Together" /><published>2022-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/together</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/together"><![CDATA[<p>We are together –</p>

<p>Perfectly imperfect and eternally beautiful –</p>

<p>Just like this world –</p>

<p>We are perpetual motion machines ーー</p>

<p>Of redemption –</p>

<p>Hope is the redemption from hopelessness –</p>

<p>Love from hate –</p>

<p>Joy from pain –</p>

<p>The time we spend together - From the time we are part –</p>

<p>From the time we were born - From the time we met –
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are together –]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">No Blanket</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/no-blanket" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No Blanket" /><published>2021-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/no-blanket</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/no-blanket"><![CDATA[<p>The urban legend is true. If you keep feeding a cat, they get as big as a lion. I’ve fed Lola grass fed wagyu steak for six months straight. She got as big as a female lion that I saw at Werribee Open Range Zoo. She still chased mice and killed native birds every once in a while. She still loved to get her chin stroked and slept on my bed. I no longer needed a blanket.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The urban legend is true. If you keep feeding a cat, they get as big as a lion. I’ve fed Lola grass fed wagyu steak for six months straight. She got as big as a female lion that I saw at Werribee Open Range Zoo. She still chased mice and killed native birds every once in a while. She still loved to get her chin stroked and slept on my bed. I no longer needed a blanket.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Too Far</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/too-far" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Too Far" /><published>2021-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/too-far</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/too-far"><![CDATA[<p>Me and my best mate, Jonesy, had a big night in the city. We started drinking at 2pm in the afternoon. It was a Friday. We knocked off work early and went to a pub. We kept drinking into the night.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>After many pints of beer and tequila shots, the bartender did the last call. The pub was closing. We decided to go to another pub.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>So, we went into a pub nearby. We walked in, saw a pool table, and started playing pool. Then, I saw a brunette girl in a black dress walking towards me. We made eye contact and I immediately felt the spark. It was one of those moments that you just knew she was up for it.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>She sat on the chair by the pool table, just opposite to where I stood. She pulled up her skirt, opened her legs and started touching herself.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I was thinking to myself: ‘Wow wow wow, how this could be happening! I just hit the jackpot! She’s hot and crazy!’
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Then, I suddenly realised that we were in a strip club. When we got in the club, both of us were too drunk to know where we were. That was when I knew we went too far.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Me and my best mate, Jonesy, had a big night in the city. We started drinking at 2pm in the afternoon. It was a Friday. We knocked off work early and went to a pub. We kept drinking into the night.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Steal Dogs From Rich People To Make Money</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/i-steal-dogs-from-rich-people-to-make-money" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Steal Dogs From Rich People To Make Money" /><published>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/stealing-dog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/i-steal-dogs-from-rich-people-to-make-money"><![CDATA[<p>My brother used to steal dogs from rich people to make money. He went to rich suburbs like Toorak or South Yarra and stole dogs from rich-looking houses. He kept them in the garage at our mother’s place. Back then, we were still living with her. She’s went into the garage because she was afraid of spiders.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>He had the whole operation set up in the garage. He had dog cages stacked up like an apartment complex. He basically built a bloody dog shelter in the garage.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>After a few days, missing dog posters would usually pop up everywhere: <em>Lost Dog, my poor pooch, such an angel, with big brown eyes, and fluffy ears etc etc</em>.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Then, he would dutifully bring the dog to the right owner. OK, nobody really expects to get cash rewards from returning a missing dog. For some crazy reasons, he always ended up getting paid. There was something special about him that made the rich people want to give him money. Was it because of his mischievous smile? Was it because of the way he stares at them with his puppy eyes with just the right length of time. Who knows? He somehow made money from returning dogs.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>All good things must come to an end.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>He stole a female pooch from an expensive-looking house in St Kilda. One of those houses with gargoyle status at the gate. She was a Pom, a fluffy little one. He didn’t know who the owner was. It didn’t matter. He took her back to the garage, his own private hack dog shelter. He waited for the missing dog posters to appear.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>It never came. After a week, he went back to the house to check on the owner.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>There was no house. It wasn’t there. He swore he went back to the right location. It was an empty land. Weeds growing everywhere. The gargoyles were still there at the gate. There was no mistake. The house was there where he stole the fluffy pooch.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>He went back to the garage where he kept the dog. To his surprise, she wasn’t there. He stared at the empty cage. She vanished into thin air just like the house. He swore she was there just before he left. He asked his mother if she had seen a dog that fit the description he gave her. Her answer was no.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>The whole thing completely spooked him out. After that, he never stole a dog from rich people to make money.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My brother used to steal dogs from rich people to make money. He went to rich suburbs like Toorak or South Yarra and stole dogs from rich-looking houses. He kept them in the garage at our mother’s place. Back then, we were still living with her. She’s went into the garage because she was afraid of spiders.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How To Mail A Diamond</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/how-to-mail-a-diamond" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Mail A Diamond" /><published>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/how-to-mail-diamond</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/how-to-mail-a-diamond"><![CDATA[<p>I sometimes wonder how diamonds get shipped from one place to another. We probably cannot send it in a parcel from the post office. Surely, that’s not reliable. How about a reputable international courier like UPC with their black vans? Nah, probably that’s not good enough either. We’re talking about diamonds here. They are forever.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Ok, so if someone wants to ship a diamond to someone else, they would hire two men in black suits with sunglasses on. They would look like Will Smith and Tommy Lee Jones from Men in Black. They always work in pairs. One of them carries a suitcase and the other one does the talking. The case is tailor-made. Inside the suitcase, they cut out a hole where the diamond can fit perfectly. One suitcase per diamond. That’s right, diamonds must be carried by a person.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>They would only use first-class tickets when they fly. When they are on the road, they only use a black limo. It is equipped with a mini bar fridge filled with mini champagne bottles. They are not gonna touch the bottle because they are on duty. What a shame.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>They must be carrying guns. Of course.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>They have a rendezvous at the destination. It’s gotta be at a discreet and private location, like a room at a hotel with no sign. They meet a receiver, open the suitcase and show the gem. Note that the receiver works alone. Always. He carries a suitcase full of cash. He also carries a gun, of course. He opens his to prove that he’s got cash. After the confirmation, both parties close the cases and exchange them. During this transaction, nobody utters a word. Just a lot of nods between them.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Yes, that’s gotta be the way to mail diamonds.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>What about Opals? Ah, Australians are loose. They would probably stuff it in a parcel and mail it with Australian Post.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I sometimes wonder how diamonds get shipped from one place to another. We probably cannot send it in a parcel from the post office. Surely, that’s not reliable. How about a reputable international courier like UPC with their black vans? Nah, probably that’s not good enough either. We’re talking about diamonds here. They are forever.]]></summary></entry></feed>