<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-09-16T10:56:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Gentle Sunlight Through the Window</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/gentle-sunlight" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gentle Sunlight Through the Window" /><published>2020-09-06T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-06T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/gentle-sunlight</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/gentle-sunlight">&lt;p&gt;It was a warm autumn afternoon. I was reading yesterday’s newspaper in my living room. I wasn’t paying attention to what the article was about. The strange mixture of nerves and excitment was taking over my mind like a tiny flying insect stuck in my ear. Nothing would have made the buzzing disappear, let alone mundane reports on daily events in the newspaper. Her late arrival was pre-empted by the text message she had sent me an hour ago. ‘I’m on my way now. Sorry, it seems the last ten months haven’t taught me punctuality.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As my eyes glazing over the same article again and again without registering its contents, I heard the shy knocking echo in the dim and narrow hallway. I quickly got off the couch and ran down to the front door. Swift, but quiet. I tried to conceal my eagerness. When I reached the dorr, I took a few deep breaths to make myself appear relaxed. My senses were sharpenedl I could tell she was nervous from the way she knocked the door.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I slowly opened the door. There she was, standing at my doorstep. She hadn’t changed except the length of her fringe, shorter than I remembered. She smiled shyly. ‘Hi.’ Our embrace was a little longer and tighter than that of two friends and a little shorter and less intimate than that of two lovers.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It had been ten months since I said Good-by to Annabelle. It was a cold winter morning. She was about to fall asleep again after the drowsy morning sex. Before I left for work, I leaned over and kissed her while she snuggled warmly under the blanket. She looked at me with her clear blue eyes. I reached my hand to her head and gently combed her tangled red hair with my fingers. The morning sunlight through the bedroom window made her eyes even clearer. She looked vulnerable and pure. Clear blue eyes and tangled red hair, sleepy and warm under the blanket. That was how I remembered her best.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that evening, she left for Italy. We did not talk about our future due to our respective ‘ignorance-is-bliss’ attitudes to our impending separation. No promises were made between us. It however seemed natural that way.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As she nonchalantly walked into the living room and threw herself on the worn-out counch and looked up at me and smiled a little.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Would you like to have something to drink?’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked. A decent thing to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘What do you have?’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She asked casually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Well, mainly water. I mean tap water. I bet you missed Melbourne tap water. It’s the finest in the world. Good for your teeth, too. But, I can make a cup of tea for you if you want to have something more exciting?’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As soon as I suggested tea, I silently cursed myself for not having milk in the fridge. I remember she liked to have tea with milk and one sugar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Water is fine, I mean &lt;i&gt;Melbourne tap water&lt;/i&gt; is fine with me, thanks.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She smiled.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I grabbed her a glass of water from the kitchen and sat clumsily next to her. Not so close as to be suggestive, but close enough to be casual and friendly. The cheap plastic yellow-framed clock on the wall suggested it was half past two. The autumn sunlight pouring through big window made the room bright and warm. The gleam of daylight made the yellow of the clock frame more striking than usual. I felt slightly annonyed by the color so being yellow and bright. I looked away from the clock. The water in the glass was cloudy from countless tiny air bubbles from the tap. So was my head from, well, I didn’t know what. The low clarity of the tap water in the glass worried me a little. The low clarity of my thoughts wasn’t helping, either. Before I commended on how the glass of water looked, Anabelle casually took a sip. She didn’t seem to care about the clarity of the water much.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I asked Annabelle about her life in Italy. She wasn’t talkative girl. She usually only said a few things at a time, always waiting for further inquiry. Unless she had been high on cocain or something. On this occasion, however, she was very talkative without having been high. She went on and on about her life in Italy and all the adventures she had there. I sat next to her and listened to her stories. I was glad that I didn’t need to make much effort to get her talking. Silence was the most awkward thing I could imagine at the time. Maybe, she thought so, too.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As she was talking, I felt that little by little, she was getting closer to me. That could have been my imagination. The way she smiled and pouted her lips seemed suggestive. It must not have been her intention. Girls instinctively make seductive gestures like that without meaning it. I always hopelessly fall for it. I was not going to this time. I tucked my hands under my thighs instead. My intention was to suggest nothing and keep the conversation going.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After we exchanged enough information regarding our last ten months, I suggested we would go out to the backyard and smoke a cigarette. I couldn’t sit still any longer with her, and besides I hadn’t smoked all morning. The autumn afternoon was delightful. It was a fine day; the air was slightly cold, and dry. The chill anticipated the imminent arrival of another winter while the dryness recalled the drought from the previous summer. I was suddently overwhelmed by how quickly time had gone by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Do you remember I was telling you that I was going to clean up my backyard when the weather got better last winter? Well, you can see I didn’t. I feel like I said that not so long ago.’ I said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Umm, I guess it seems like nothing has changed although I’m sure a lot of things have.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She exhailed.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I watched the smoke dissipating in the air, considering the time lost. We need a reminder. Something like the accumulated fallen leaves to show us time has passed and things have changed.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lit my cigarette and slowly filled my lung with smoke. The first cigarette of day is always good. Much better than the last. Anabelle was standing in the middle of the yard, gracefully absorbing the warm autumn sunlight like an iguana in Galapagos Island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘It’s a beautiful day.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She sounded as if she had said that to herself. Her eyes were closed and her voice was relaxed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Yes, you look so beautiful, too.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I almost said that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, I instead made a grumbling noise, which resembled indifferent, ‘Yeah’. The seamless blue sky above us was as clear as her eyes. I wanted to say something clever or funny. Nothing came out. All I could was just watching her dumbly and pretending that I was relaxed and at ease with myself and the situation. I threw my half-smoked cigarette on to the ground and stepped on it, making sure it wasn’t burning anymore. The butt looked crooked and miserable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Would you like to have some tea now? We are out of milk at the moment, so I think green tea is the best bet.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘I dont mind. That sounds good. Green tea is tea after all.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said without turning her head, her eyes still closed, soaking up the warmth of the sun.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I was pouring freshly brewed green tea, I heard Annabelle lightly slipping back into the house like a stray cat. I carried the cups to the living room and clumsily put them on the table. She was quietly sitting on the couch, staring at the ray of light pouring through the window. Tiny dust particles twinkled like stars in the Milky Way. Her glance slowly moved to the steam coming from the cups. Rising and disappearing into the Milky Way in the microcosm of my living room. I sat next to her without a word.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, her monile phone rang. Silence broken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Execuse me. Oh, thanks for the tea.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She reached her hand to her coat pocket to fish out her phone. As she was chatting on the phone, I kept staring at the steam raising from the tea. It was still too hot to drink. Annabelle still talking on the phone. No, nothing else to do for me apart from staring at the tea cups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘OK, I’ll see you soon, then.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;End of the conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘I’m sorry, babe. I have to catch up with my friends now. I’ve been away for too long and want to catch up with everyone before I start working and get busy.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘That’s cool. I’ll walk you out.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said calmly to conceal my disappointment. What else could I have said?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She headed down the dim, narrow hallway. I followd her as casually as possible, hoping she would not detect growing heaviness of my steps. I came close to tell her not to leave. But, the hallway wasn’t long enough for my indecisive mind. As she carelessly flung open the door, she turned around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘I wish I could stay longer, but, I really gotta go. When can I see you again? We should catch up for a drink?’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was really going to tell her not to leave. The words somehow stuck in my throat, hanging and nagging there like a small fish bone from a deep-fried flounder stuck in the throat. Instead, I calmly said,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Well, that sounds good, but I’m moving to London very soon. I’ve got a new job there. I’m not sure if I have time to see you again.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Oh, really? You didn’t tell me that. You always leave important things out when we talk. Oh, god. When are you leaving? What happens to your room?’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a second, her eyes gleamed with disappointment and confustion. Or was that my imagination? She might not have cared as much.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I explained her that I was going to the airport to catch a midnight flight in 10 hours and I didn’t really need to get rid of much because my brother was taking over my room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Well, I’m not sure when I’m coming back. I suppose it depends on how well things go over there.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I said weakly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Oh well, that sounds great. Congratulations.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She sounded calm. She always kept her cool. I tried to act cool, too. I tried to come up with something sweet to say. Nothing. My pathetic mind, as blank as the list of my life achievement.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I could think of anything to say, she hugged me briefly and we bid a dry farewell to each other. I stood and watched her disappear in the autumn sunlight. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was back in my living room. It was warm and quiet. Bathing in the warm silence, I stared at two teacups on the table. Annabelle’s on the left and mine on the right. Neither of us had taken a sip. No steam rising anymore. The ray of light was gone, too. The Milky Way, gone. My microcosm, imploded. The whole afternoon seemed like a dream. I wasn’t even sure if she had been here. She left no trace except the untouched cup of green tea. I told myself that I’d see Annabelle again in the future. There would always be something to remind us of the irrevocable passage of time between Annabelle and I, like the soiled leaves in my neglected backyard. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clock on the wall read half past two.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">It was a warm autumn afternoon. I was reading yesterday’s newspaper in my living room. I wasn’t paying attention to what the article was about. The strange mixture of nerves and excitment was taking over my mind like a tiny flying insect stuck in my ear. Nothing would have made the buzzing disappear, let alone mundane reports on daily events in the newspaper. Her late arrival was pre-empted by the text message she had sent me an hour ago. ‘I’m on my way now. Sorry, it seems the last ten months haven’t taught me punctuality.’</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fake Brick</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-brick" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fake Brick" /><published>2020-09-06T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-06T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-brick</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-brick">&lt;p&gt;I usually carry around a fake brick made of styroform (custom-made from China). Whenever dickheads try to fuck with us, I take out my fake brick and crack it with my fist in front of ‘em.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any dumb arse would figure out what’s going on. ‘Oh, shit. Here’s a crazy Asian cracking a real hard brick with his bear fist (flash back of a scene from a Bruce Lee movie in his head). No no no, better not fuck with him!’ It always works because who wants to fuck with Bruce Lee?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, the street is tough. Everybody tries to fuck with us. I always must have a few tricks up my sleeve to get out of troubles.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">I usually carry around a fake brick made of styroform (custom-made from China). Whenever dickheads try to fuck with us, I take out my fake brick and crack it with my fist in front of ‘em.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Birthday Party</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/birthday-party" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Birthday Party" /><published>2020-09-06T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-06T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/birthday-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/birthday-party">&lt;p&gt;Before I started playing in the Garbage Collection, I was doing a PhD in Genetics. I was at some birthday party in a hip pub in Richmond. I tried to drink as much free booze as I can while the bar tab lasted. I think I’ve drunk 70% of the tab all by myself. Free drink was a rare delight in those days. This was way before the life of sex, drug and Rock’ n’ Roll. I’m wearing a cream-coloured leather jacket from an Opshop in Brighton and a pair of vintage black-framed glasses, going for nerd chic. These people are my fellow science nerd friends who’d get my esoteric DNA jokes. I was preaching the benefit of LSD for science. After all, the legend tells that Francis Crick was walking on the beach on acid when he came up with the double helix structure.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not long after the photo was taken, the guy next to me, Brenton, hijacked the DJ booth with his iPod and played Thriller so that he can show everyone his break-dance skills. The night went wilder and wilder. We went onto a club in the city later. I picked up a really cute brunette girl at the club and made her climb an abandoned cillo in Collingwood to watch the sunrise with me. We’ve spent all day in her bed.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never called her back.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">Before I started playing in the Garbage Collection, I was doing a PhD in Genetics. I was at some birthday party in a hip pub in Richmond. I tried to drink as much free booze as I can while the bar tab lasted. I think I’ve drunk 70% of the tab all by myself. Free drink was a rare delight in those days. This was way before the life of sex, drug and Rock’ n’ Roll. I’m wearing a cream-coloured leather jacket from an Opshop in Brighton and a pair of vintage black-framed glasses, going for nerd chic. These people are my fellow science nerd friends who’d get my esoteric DNA jokes. I was preaching the benefit of LSD for science. After all, the legend tells that Francis Crick was walking on the beach on acid when he came up with the double helix structure.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tunnel</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tunnel" /><published>2020-01-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel">&lt;p&gt;     I dragged my feet into the dark tunnel. There was neither day nor night. There was no light. I simply lost my sight. Not a single speck of star beamed a ray of hope. Not a single drop of rain redeemed my dry soul.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;     In summer, it burned red-hot coals like the industrial garbage furnace. In winter, it froze everything, even my bones. Neither spring nor autumn ever came. There was neither the joy of being born nor the calamity of the last dying day.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;     So, I stopped writing poems in the tunnel of darkness. I’ve burned my words in summer. I froze and shattered them in winter. I would find neither a single dime nor rhyme in my pocket. I didn’t think I deserved either one of them, anyway.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">     I dragged my feet into the dark tunnel. There was neither day nor night. There was no light. I simply lost my sight. Not a single speck of star beamed a ray of hope. Not a single drop of rain redeemed my dry soul.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Metric</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metric" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Metric" /><published>2020-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metrics</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metric">&lt;p&gt;creating of dissatisfaction –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;is the metric –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for – customer – satisfaction
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">creating of dissatisfaction –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Faith</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Faith" /><published>2020-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith">&lt;p&gt;you have faith in everything –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
but – me –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i know&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    i don’t deserve it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    why not?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">you have faith in everything –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Manifesto</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Manifesto" /><published>2020-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-07T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto">&lt;p&gt;Word created – the – World&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words created the God –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God is a word&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I speak these Words –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am the creater of the World
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">Word created – the – World</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moment of Maddness</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/moment-of-maddness" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moment of Maddness" /><published>2020-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/moment-of-madness</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/moment-of-maddness">&lt;p&gt;A moment of madness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m waiting for you –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No consequence – No future –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll embrace you with my arms wide open&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;with clarity – purpose – deamon – angel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of a martyr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;strapped in a ticking time bomb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at the Federation Square 3pm –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunny Sunday afternoon
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A moment of maddness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come to me – Come to me –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reasoning will be a retrospective spectacle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contemplated in a gap between your baby and womb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;where I have no part to play&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m tired of –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;justifying my will with a perfect will –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no such will anyway
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A moment of maddness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free me – Free me –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defy the law of gravity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the power of reasoning –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A healthy dose of hope –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold stare of the 3-eyed skull&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;with 20-20-20 vision&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dope, doctor, dog, dough, doctorin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;documentation, Dostoevsky&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burn them all
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">A moment of madness</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hero Dose</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/hero-dose" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hero Dose" /><published>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/hero-dose</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/hero-dose">&lt;p&gt;9 grams
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 grams — Big doses
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 grams — Small doses
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9 grams — Hero dose
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">9 grams</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nail Gun</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/nail-gun" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nail Gun" /><published>2020-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/nail-gun</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/nail-gun">&lt;p&gt;I fired a nail gun&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    into Emma’s right breast
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;click, click, click, click, click
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She blead and cried
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I held her in my arms
and gently pulled all the nails.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sincerely apologized to her
– I am sorry. I didn’t mean to hurt you
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said – it’s ok, I will forgive you
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The holes left by the nails on her breast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;remained open and hollow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everytime she looks at her breast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is reminded&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that I was the one who&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fired the nail gun at her&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;perfect breast
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">I fired a nail gun</summary></entry></feed>