<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-27T08:50:10+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">No Blanket</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/no-blanket" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="No Blanket" /><published>2021-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/no-blanket</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/no-blanket">&lt;p&gt;The urban legend is true. If you keep feeding a cat, they get as big as a lion. I’ve fed Lola grass fed wagyu steak for six months straight. She got as big as a female lion that I saw at Werribee Open Range Zoo. She still chased mice and killed native birds every once in a while. She still loved to get her chin stroked and slept on my bed. I no longer needed a blanket.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">The urban legend is true. If you keep feeding a cat, they get as big as a lion. I’ve fed Lola grass fed wagyu steak for six months straight. She got as big as a female lion that I saw at Werribee Open Range Zoo. She still chased mice and killed native birds every once in a while. She still loved to get her chin stroked and slept on my bed. I no longer needed a blanket.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Too Far</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/too-far" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Too Far" /><published>2021-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/too-far</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/too-far">&lt;p&gt;Me and my best mate, Jonesy, had a big night in the city. We started drinking at 2pm in the afternoon. It was a Friday. We knocked off work early and went to a pub. We kept drinking into the night.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After many pints of beer and tequila shots, the bartender did the last call. The pub was closing. We decided to go to another pub. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we went into a pub nearby. We walked in, saw a pool table, and started playing pool. Then, I saw a brunette girl in a black dress walking towards me. We made eye contact and I immediately felt the spark. It was one of those moments that you just knew she was up for it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She sat on the chair by the pool table, just opposite to where I stood. She pulled up her skirt, opened her legs and started touching herself.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was thinking to myself: ‘Wow wow wow, how this could be happening! I just hit the jackpot! She’s hot and crazy!’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, I suddenly realised that we were in a strip club. When we got in the club, both of us were too drunk to even realise it was a strip club. That was when I knew we went too far.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">Me and my best mate, Jonesy, had a big night in the city. We started drinking at 2pm in the afternoon. It was a Friday. We knocked off work early and went to a pub. We kept drinking into the night.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I Steal Dogs From Rich People To Make Money</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/i-steal-dogs-from-rich-people-to-make-money" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Steal Dogs From Rich People To Make Money" /><published>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/stealing-dog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/i-steal-dogs-from-rich-people-to-make-money">&lt;p&gt;My brother used to steal dogs from rich people to make money. He went to rich suburbs like Toorak or South Yarra and stole dogs from rich-looking houses. He kept them in the garage at our mother’s place. Back then, we were still living with her. She’s went into the garage because she was afraid of spiders.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had the whole operation set up in the garage. He had dog cages stacked up like an apartment complex. He basically built a bloody dog shelter in the garage.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a few days, missing dog posters would usually pop up everywhere: &lt;em&gt;Lost Dog, my poor pooch, such an angel, with big brown eyes, and fluffy ears etc etc&lt;/em&gt;.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, he would dutifully bring the dog to the right owner. OK, nobody really expects to get cash rewards from returning a missing dog. For some crazy reasons, he always ended up getting paid. There was something special about him that made the rich people want to give him money. Was it because of his mischievous smile? Was it because of the way he stares at them with his puppy eyes with just the right length of time. Who knows? He somehow made money from returning dogs.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All good things must come to an end.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He stole a female pooch from an expensive-looking house in St Kilda. One of those houses with gargoyle status at the gate. She was a Pom, a fluffy little one. He didn’t know who the owner was. It didn’t matter. He took her back to the garage, his own private hack dog shelter. He waited for the missing dog posters to appear.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It never came. After a week, he went back to the house to check on the owner.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was no house. It wasn’t there. He swore he went back to the right location. It was an empty land. Weeds growing everywhere. The gargoyles were still there at the gate. There was no mistake. The house was there where he stole the fluffy pooch.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He went back to the garage where he kept the dog. To his surprise, she wasn’t there. He stared at the empty cage. She vanished into thin air just like the house. He swore she was there just before he left. He asked his mother if she had seen a dog that fit the description he gave her. Her answer was no.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The whole thing completely spooked him out. After that, he never stole a dog from rich people to make money.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">My brother used to steal dogs from rich people to make money. He went to rich suburbs like Toorak or South Yarra and stole dogs from rich-looking houses. He kept them in the garage at our mother’s place. Back then, we were still living with her. She’s went into the garage because she was afraid of spiders. He had the whole operation set up in the garage. He had dog cages stacked up like an apartment complex. He basically built a bloody dog shelter in the garage. After a few days, missing dog posters would usually pop up everywhere: Lost Dog, my poor pooch, such an angel, with big brown eyes, and fluffy ears etc etc. Then, he would dutifully bring the dog to the right owner. OK, nobody really expects to get cash rewards from returning a missing dog. For some crazy reasons, he always ended up getting paid. There was something special about him that made the rich people want to give him money. Was it because of his mischievous smile? Was it because of the way he stares at them with his puppy eyes with just the right length of time. Who knows? He somehow made money from returning dogs. All good things must come to an end. He stole a female pooch from an expensive-looking house in St Kilda. One of those houses with gargoyle status at the gate. She was a Pom, a fluffy little one. He didn’t know who the owner was. It didn’t matter. He took her back to the garage, his own private hack dog shelter. He waited for the missing dog posters to appear.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How To Mail A Diamond</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/how-to-mail-a-diamond" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Mail A Diamond" /><published>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/how-to-mail-diamond</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/how-to-mail-a-diamond">&lt;p&gt;I sometimes wonder how diamonds get shipped from one place to another. We probably cannot send it in a parcel from the post office. Surely, that’s not reliable. How about a reputable international courier like UPC with their black vans? Nah, probably that’s not good enough either. We’re talking about diamonds here. They are forever.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, so if someone wants to ship a diamond to someone else, they would hire two men in black suits with sunglasses on. They would look like Will Smith and Tommy Lee Jones from Men in Black. They always work in pairs. One of them carries a suitcase and the other one does the talking. The case is tailor-made. Inside the suitcase, they cut out a hole where the diamond can fit perfectly. One suitcase per diamond. That’s right, diamonds must be carried by a person.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They would only use first-class tickets when they fly. When they are on the road, they only use a black limo. It is equipped with a mini bar fridge filled with mini champagne bottles. They are not gonna touch the bottle because they are on duty. What a shame.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They must be carrying guns. Of course.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They have a rendezvous at the destination. It’s gotta be at a discreet and private location, like a room at a hotel with no sign. They meet a receiver, open the suitcase and show the gem. Note that the receiver works alone. Always. He carries a suitcase full of cash. He also carries a gun, of course. He opens his to prove that he’s got cash. After the confirmation, both parties close the cases and exchange them. During this transaction, nobody utters a word. Just a lot of nods between them.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, that’s gotta be the way to mail diamonds.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What about Opals? Ah, Australians are loose. They would probably stuff it in a parcel and mail it with Australian Post.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">I sometimes wonder how diamonds get shipped from one place to another. We probably cannot send it in a parcel from the post office. Surely, that’s not reliable. How about a reputable international courier like UPC with their black vans? Nah, probably that’s not good enough either. We’re talking about diamonds here. They are forever. Ok, so if someone wants to ship a diamond to someone else, they would hire two men in black suits with sunglasses on. They would look like Will Smith and Tommy Lee Jones from Men in Black. They always work in pairs. One of them carries a suitcase and the other one does the talking. The case is tailor-made. Inside the suitcase, they cut out a hole where the diamond can fit perfectly. One suitcase per diamond. That’s right, diamonds must be carried by a person. They would only use first-class tickets when they fly. When they are on the road, they only use a black limo. It is equipped with a mini bar fridge filled with mini champagne bottles. They are not gonna touch the bottle because they are on duty. What a shame. They must be carrying guns. Of course. They have a rendezvous at the destination. It’s gotta be at a discreet and private location, like a room at a hotel with no sign. They meet a receiver, open the suitcase and show the gem. Note that the receiver works alone. Always. He carries a suitcase full of cash. He also carries a gun, of course. He opens his to prove that he’s got cash. After the confirmation, both parties close the cases and exchange them. During this transaction, nobody utters a word. Just a lot of nods between them. Yes, that’s gotta be the way to mail diamonds. What about Opals? Ah, Australians are loose. They would probably stuff it in a parcel and mail it with Australian Post.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Rejection Letter</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/rejection-letter" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rejection Letter" /><published>2021-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-06-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/rejection-letter</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/rejection-letter">&lt;p&gt;Dear Taka,
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I appreciate the time you took to come in for the physical performance trial for my mating partner position the other night. You were not selected to return to my apartment. I have already received applications from many qualified candidates, several of whom are taller, better-looking, and more masculine, having bigger cars, balls, and penises and greater earning capabilities, key job requirements.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for participating in the trial with me. I enjoyed meeting you and appreciate your interest in applying for my opening position. I also appreciate the time you invested in foreplay although I feel that you could have spent a little longer and made a little bit more effort.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish you success in your ongoing mating partner search. Please do not consider re-applying for the position for which you are assessed as ‘not adequately qualified’. It will be a waste of time for both of us.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Betty&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">Dear Taka,</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apocalypse</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/apocalypse" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apocalypse" /><published>2021-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/apocalypse</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/apocalypse">&lt;p&gt;Pens and papers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stone walls and chalks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaves and blood,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dirt on the ground,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fallen branches from His apple tree,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sand on the beach,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A piece of wood floated from Afrika,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where we all came from,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or the sea shell that she sells by the sea shore –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Letter in a glass bottle,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a cork stopper,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tidal force from the lunatics,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Mother’s breast milk –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A message on a dove’s leg,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sink your teeth into the mycelium network,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the heavenly neural connections –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whisper into a paper cup,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connected to the other paper cup,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Her umbilical cord –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We blamed Her,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, it was all His fault –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">Pens and papers</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Toxic Relationship</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/toxic-relationship" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Toxic Relationship" /><published>2021-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/toxic-relationship</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/toxic-relationship">&lt;p&gt;This - is - Toxic –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My relationship with poetry –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stare at my muse,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her eyes, her wrist,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her neck, her lips,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her hips, her navel,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her hair, her pubic hair,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her vagina, her anus,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her, her, her, she, she, she,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Promised land, Oasis in the desert,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fucking Cock Lock,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nipple Clamps,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day after day,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Week after week,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes month after month,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s always there,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, she won’t let me touch her –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blank Page –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same – Blank Page –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I jerk off,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to start the ritual from the start again –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try not to –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, I sometimes masturbate - in – Secret –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(She know about it, she’s just lying beside me, not asleep and feels the movement of my hand, but she won’t say a word),&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ejaculation on the white blank page –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because she is so hard to get,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or tantra went too long to be productive –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new blank page followed by,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing to show for –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, out of Nowhere –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Out of the Blue,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blue Moon Dust,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full Moon, New Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blood Moon, Black Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wet Moon, Super Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harvest Moon, Hunter Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wolf Moon, Snow Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Worm Moon, Pink Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flower Moon, Honey Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buck Moon, Beaver Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Lunar Eclipse,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adelaide Lunatic Asylum,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dark side of the Moon,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thou Shall Be Free,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By Moonlover –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She pulls me in,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am in,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Movements,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back and forth,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upward and downward,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Past and Future,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Right Now,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right inside the lines,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside of the lines,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Between the lines,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In front of the lines,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Behind the lines,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the lines,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words, words, words, words, words…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bang,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whole body orgasm –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Giving rise to – This –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">This - is - Toxic –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gather Animals</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/gather-animals" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gather Animals" /><published>2021-05-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-05-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/gather-animals</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/gather-animals">&lt;p&gt;Yeah I know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just between you and me,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been building an ark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wrath will come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Better be ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spring is almost here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must be planning to visit me very soon?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please gather pairs of various animals that you come across.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">Yeah I know.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Christian</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/christian" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Christian" /><published>2021-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/christian</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/christian">&lt;p&gt;‘I got a mate and everyone calls him Buddha. Do you know why?’ Jim asked.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Is he fat?’ I replied.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Nah, his name is Christian. That’s why everybody calls him Buddha.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Ok, if we got a mate called Muhammad, can we call him Jesus, then?’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Nah, they wouldn’t like it. The more close-minded the organisation is, the less it has a sense of humor.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘I think you are right. Let’s call him Buddha, too, then.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">‘I got a mate and everyone calls him Buddha. Do you know why?’ Jim asked.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">40th Birthday Party</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/40th-bday-party" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="40th Birthday Party" /><published>2021-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/40th-bday-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/40th-bday-party">&lt;p&gt;Jin said, ‘I have no plan for the next 10 years. No plan at all.’ on his 40’s birthday. What a beautiful sentiment it is. I’m turning 40 next year. I hope to say the same thing. As we get older, we know more about the place we were in this world. We fine-tune what we want out of our life. We worry less about what we don’t have. We care less about the society of expectations. I’ve been worrying about those things all my life and didn’t end up achieving any of them. I’m still single. I am a migrant and do not have family in this country. I am lonely. I still live in a rental property. I don’t have any savings. I have a shit job. It doesn’t matter. If I could accept who I am and snatch the joy out of this crap thing called life, I don’t need to have a plan. I can be myself and keep going forwards on my own train.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what, Jin went home with a beautiful 26 years old brunette that night. He wasn’t even trying. She was literally throwing herself at him. I was thinking to myself, ‘Fuck, how does that happen?’. Well, it was his birthday. A birthday boy needs to get laid no matter how old he is. It’s a plan that the universe installed for all of us.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">Jin said, ‘I have no plan for the next 10 years. No plan at all.’ on his 40’s birthday. What a beautiful sentiment it is. I’m turning 40 next year. I hope to say the same thing. As we get older, we know more about the place we were in this world. We fine-tune what we want out of our life. We worry less about what we don’t have. We care less about the society of expectations. I’ve been worrying about those things all my life and didn’t end up achieving any of them. I’m still single. I am a migrant and do not have family in this country. I am lonely. I still live in a rental property. I don’t have any savings. I have a shit job. It doesn’t matter. If I could accept who I am and snatch the joy out of this crap thing called life, I don’t need to have a plan. I can be myself and keep going forwards on my own train. You know what, Jin went home with a beautiful 26 years old brunette that night. He wasn’t even trying. She was literally throwing herself at him. I was thinking to myself, ‘Fuck, how does that happen?’. Well, it was his birthday. A birthday boy needs to get laid no matter how old he is. It’s a plan that the universe installed for all of us.</summary></entry></feed>