<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-04T06:22:38+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Dating Apps</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/dating-apps" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dating Apps" /><published>2023-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/dating-apps</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/dating-apps"><![CDATA[<p>My friend’s wisdom on dating apps, ‘the difference between us and them is that we are running the race and they are at the goal waiting for which one comes first’.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friend’s wisdom on dating apps, ‘the difference between us and them is that we are running the race and they are at the goal waiting for which one comes first’.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why do you keep reading to me?</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/why-do-you" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why do you keep reading to me?" /><published>2023-02-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-02-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/why-do-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/why-do-you"><![CDATA[<p>Why do you keep reading to me –</p>

<p>Let me keep your house key –</p>

<p>Send me flowers –</p>

<p>Keep the water fresh –</p>

<p>In the vase for the aforementioned flowers?
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Why do you keep bringing the eggs –</p>

<p>From the chicken in your garden –</p>

<p>And Fish that you catch –</p>

<p>With the worms –</p>

<p>From the aforementioned garden?
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Why do you keep telling me –</p>

<p>Your daughter cuts the potatoes –</p>

<p>The way I taught her –</p>

<p>Keep bringing me the potatoes –</p>

<p>You cut in the aforementioned way?
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Why do you keep coming to my house –</p>

<p>Keep borrowing books from my bookshelf –</p>

<p>Pruning the shrubs in my field –</p>

<p>Water my vegetable plants –</p>

<p>Grow in the aforementioned field?
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do you keep reading to me –]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fly a kite</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/fly-a-kite" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fly a kite" /><published>2023-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-01-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/fly-a-kite</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/fly-a-kite"><![CDATA[<p>Fly a kite into the storm of my sorrow,</p>

<p>It will shred it into a million pieces.
<br /><br />
Sail through the flood of my rage,</p>

<p>Nobody will survive.
<br /><br />
Walk across the desert of my loneliness,</p>

<p>There is no oasis.
<br /><br />
Sleigh into the blizzard of my jealousy,</p>

<p>You will lose your digits.
<br /><br />
Throw a rock into the ocean of my love,</p>

<p>It will sink forever,</p>

<p>Into the bottomless bottom,</p>

<p>A pit of darkness,</p>

<p>No way to float back up,</p>

<p>Until getting through,</p>

<p>To the other side.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fly a kite into the storm of my sorrow,]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Swirl</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/swirl" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Swirl" /><published>2022-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/swirl</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/swirl"><![CDATA[<p>I firmly had my feet on the ground. I knew which way was up and which way was down. Then, I suddenly realised that I was upside down or downside up. I lost the direction of the gravity. I was in a swirl, spinning around and losing control. Am I ascending to heaven or descending to hell? Am I exploding into space or shrinking into a singularity? Am I a fish or a squirrel?
<br /><br />
Then, I saw you, Allen. You asked me if I was your angel. You’re beautiful, but no, you’re not my type. I’ve never read all the verses from Song of Myself. It’s too long and too self-indulgent. You horny bastard! Get me high and I might suck your cock. Where is Jack? Can we hitch-hike out of this mess?
<br /><br />
I suddenly found myself alone in a vacuum, gasping for air. Actually, I wasn’t in a vacuum. I just forgot how to breathe. Breathe in and breathe out. That was all I needed to do. It was that simple.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I firmly had my feet on the ground. I knew which way was up and which way was down. Then, I suddenly realised that I was upside down or downside up. I lost the direction of the gravity. I was in a swirl, spinning around and losing control. Am I ascending to heaven or descending to hell? Am I exploding into space or shrinking into a singularity? Am I a fish or a squirrel? Then, I saw you, Allen. You asked me if I was your angel. You’re beautiful, but no, you’re not my type. I’ve never read all the verses from Song of Myself. It’s too long and too self-indulgent. You horny bastard! Get me high and I might suck your cock. Where is Jack? Can we hitch-hike out of this mess? I suddenly found myself alone in a vacuum, gasping for air. Actually, I wasn’t in a vacuum. I just forgot how to breathe. Breathe in and breathe out. That was all I needed to do. It was that simple.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Aged Carer</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/aged-carer" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Aged Carer" /><published>2022-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/aged-carer</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/aged-carer"><![CDATA[<p>When I was living in Japan, my job required me to visit women’s prisons. I worked as a salesman for a company that sells correspondence vocational education.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Women’s prisons in Japan are run only by women. Even the prison guards are women. Female prisoners are deprived of men.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Apparently, there are always a few prisoners who start taking off their clothes whenever they see a man. No matter how ugly he is, it really doesn’t matter. They get so excited about the mere presence of opposite-sex. Taking off their clothes results in a punishment. They have to spend a period of time in an isolation room without any window. They don’t care. They risk it anyway. In the moment of madness, the animal instinct kicks in.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>When I visited a jail for the first time, a young woman prisoner took off her clothes as I was walking by her cell. She put her right fist up in her vagina. Before the prison guard had time to get in her cell and beat her up, she managed to have an intense shaking orgasm.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>After the incident, she was sent to an isolation cell for 14 days. She eventually completed training to be an aged carer before she was released. I think of her whenever I see an aged care center.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was living in Japan, my job required me to visit women’s prisons. I worked as a salesman for a company that sells correspondence vocational education.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Caught Red Handed in Japan</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/redhanded-in-japan" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Caught Red Handed in Japan" /><published>2022-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-06-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/redhanded-in-japan</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/redhanded-in-japan"><![CDATA[<p>When I went to Japan last time, I got arrested and spent 2 weeks in jail.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I was making graffiti in Shibuya and two police officers came. I was using red spray paint and got literally caught red-handed. I got arrested and put in a detention center. Someone from the Australian embassy visited me there. I was told I would have to spend the minimum of 3 months and the maximum of 8 years if I was to be charged. I was stressed. It would suck to spend that much time in jail.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I was sharing a cell with 2 people, the old and young. The old guy was arrested for tax fraud. He didn’t speak English at all. He had a photo of his Lamborghini. He looked at the photo all the time. The young one spoke English. He got arrested for robbing a liquor store.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Food was good there. We had miso soup every meal.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I didn’t get charged. I was released after 2 weeks. That was how I got caught red-handed in Japan.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I went to Japan last time, I got arrested and spent 2 weeks in jail.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Slow Grind</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/slow-grind" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Slow Grind" /><published>2022-05-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-05-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/slow-grind</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/slow-grind"><![CDATA[<p>I snorted a line of coke and dropped a few shroom caps before going to the Slow Grind at the Loop Bar in the city. It was Jane’s birthday and she wanted to dance all night. As I was dancing on the floor to Richie 1250’s sleazy 80’s slow dance tunes, a fat girl dropped a tab of acid in my mouth. Jane had a bag of MD and let me have some. I took the bag and headed for the male toilet. Her female friend whose name I never found out followed me into the toilet cubicle. As I was scooping the powder with my key, she took off her pants and started peeing in front of me. ‘I hope you’re not feeling uncomfortable. I just need to pee.’
<br /><br /></p>

<p>Every now and then, I think about her beautiful shaven vagina and masturbate.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I snorted a line of coke and dropped a few shroom caps before going to the Slow Grind at the Loop Bar in the city. It was Jane’s birthday and she wanted to dance all night. As I was dancing on the floor to Richie 1250’s sleazy 80’s slow dance tunes, a fat girl dropped a tab of acid in my mouth. Jane had a bag of MD and let me have some. I took the bag and headed for the male toilet. Her female friend whose name I never found out followed me into the toilet cubicle. As I was scooping the powder with my key, she took off her pants and started peeing in front of me. ‘I hope you’re not feeling uncomfortable. I just need to pee.’]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Car Park</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/car-park" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Car Park" /><published>2022-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/car-park</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/car-park"><![CDATA[<p>While I was snorting coke in the toilet cubicle with Sam, Nick was having a telephone sex in the car park at Eureka community center. It was intermittently drizzling and the air was already cold. The daylight saving was gonna end tomorrow. It was the first Saturday of April. Quang told us that the reason why we use the word dozen for a collection of 12 things was that we used to have twelve fingers. We lost them somehow along the way. The humans collectively decided to forget about them. I had to keep going. There was so much booze and I was so far from home.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I was snorting coke in the toilet cubicle with Sam, Nick was having a telephone sex in the car park at Eureka community center. It was intermittently drizzling and the air was already cold. The daylight saving was gonna end tomorrow. It was the first Saturday of April. Quang told us that the reason why we use the word dozen for a collection of 12 things was that we used to have twelve fingers. We lost them somehow along the way. The humans collectively decided to forget about them. I had to keep going. There was so much booze and I was so far from home.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Body of Water</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/body-of-water" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Body of Water" /><published>2022-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/body-of-water</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/body-of-water"><![CDATA[<p>As I descended, I saw a body of water below.</p>

<p>A log was floating on the water.</p>

<p>One end was burned black and the other was cut clean.</p>

<p>I grabbed the clean end,</p>

<p>and carefully traced the concentric rings one by one with my finger.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>A piece of dirty yellowish brown cloth was floating on the water.</p>

<p>I swam towards the artefact to inspect it,</p>

<p>It was a dead body of me.</p>

<p>My feet touched the sandy bottom and I thought to myself,</p>

<p>the shore is near.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>I stood on the land, on the wet sand.</p>

<p>Charcoaled wood pieces, campfire remains,</p>

<p>I walked towards the sand dunes with tiny crabs,</p>

<p>Towards the saltbush shrubs before sea level rise and storm surge.</p>

<p>In the twilight of the empire, I saw two red moons in the sky.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I descended, I saw a body of water below.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The origin of pole jumping</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/the-origin-of-pole-jumping" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The origin of pole jumping" /><published>2022-03-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/poll-jumping</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/the-origin-of-pole-jumping"><![CDATA[<p>Pole jumping, also known as pole vaulting, is a competitive sport where the athletes compete against each other on how high they can jump by using a long flexible stick.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>The origin of pole jumping goes way back before humans invented a bridge. Our ancestors used a long stick made out of a tree to boost themselves to jump over rivers. It was an essential survival skill.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>We had to to stop them from crossing the river. They hate water. After all the bridges were destroyed, the only method for us to cross rivers was to use a long flexible stick. You would run towards the bank, stick it on the ground, and propel yourself to the other side, just like a pole jumper.
<br /><br /></p>

<p>We have gone back to the way of our ancestors.
<br /><br /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pole jumping, also known as pole vaulting, is a competitive sport where the athletes compete against each other on how high they can jump by using a long flexible stick.]]></summary></entry></feed>