<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-03-07T02:52:46+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Christian</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/christian" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Christian" /><published>2021-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/christian</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/christian">&lt;p&gt;‘I got a mate and everyone calls him Buddha. Do you know why?’ Jim asked.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Is he fat?’ I replied.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Nah, his name is Christian. That’s why everybody calls him Buddha.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Ok, if we got a mate called Muhammad, can we call him Jesus, then?’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Nah, they wouldn’t like it. The more close-minded the organisation is, the less it has a sense of humor.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘I think you are right. Let’s call him Buddha too then.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">‘I got a mate and everyone calls him Buddha. Do you know why?’ Jim asked.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">40th Birthday Party</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/40th-bday-party" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="40th Birthday Party" /><published>2021-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/40th-bday-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/40th-bday-party">&lt;p&gt;Jin said, ‘I have no plan for the next 10 years. No plan at all.’ on his 40’s birthday. What a beautiful sentiment it is. I’m turning 40 next year. I hope to say the same thing. As we get older, we know more about the place we were in this world. We fine-tune what we want out of our life. We worry less about what we don’t have. We care less about the society of expectations. I’ve been worrying about those things all my life and didn’t end up achieving any of them. I’m still single. I am a migrant and do not have family in this country. I am lonely. I still live in a rental property. I don’t have any savings. I have a shit job. It doesn’t matter. If I could accept who I am and snatch the joy out of this crap thing called life, I don’t need to have a plan. I can be myself and keep going forwards on my own train.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what, Jin went home with a beautiful 26 years old brunette that night. He wasn’t even trying. She was literally throwing herself at him. I was thinking to myself, ‘Fuck, how does that happen?’. Well, it was his birthday. A birthday boy needs to get laid no matter how old he is. It’s a plan that the universe installed for all of us.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">Jin said, ‘I have no plan for the next 10 years. No plan at all.’ on his 40’s birthday. What a beautiful sentiment it is. I’m turning 40 next year. I hope to say the same thing. As we get older, we know more about the place we were in this world. We fine-tune what we want out of our life. We worry less about what we don’t have. We care less about the society of expectations. I’ve been worrying about those things all my life and didn’t end up achieving any of them. I’m still single. I am a migrant and do not have family in this country. I am lonely. I still live in a rental property. I don’t have any savings. I have a shit job. It doesn’t matter. If I could accept who I am and snatch the joy out of this crap thing called life, I don’t need to have a plan. I can be myself and keep going forwards on my own train. You know what, Jin went home with a beautiful 26 years old brunette that night. He wasn’t even trying. She was literally throwing herself at him. I was thinking to myself, ‘Fuck, how does that happen?’. Well, it was his birthday. A birthday boy needs to get laid no matter how old he is. It’s a plan that the universe installed for all of us.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Silver Spoon</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/silver-spoon" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Silver Spoon" /><published>2020-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/sliver-spoon</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/silver-spoon">&lt;p&gt;Food fed by a Silver Spoon –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Easy – to spit It out –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Easy – to forget about It&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And completely occupy Myself –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
With – a – Thought –
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How Good it’d have been tasted –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had the Spoon been Gold
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">Food fed by a Silver Spoon –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Human Front Manifesto</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/human-front-manifesto" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Human Front Manifesto" /><published>2020-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/human-front-manifesto</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/human-front-manifesto">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opening statement&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Human Front is a military organisation to engage in an imminent space war against hostile aliens. Our primary goal is to prevent the aliens from enslaving our minds and bodies at all costs.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description of the enemy&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have little knowledge regarding their biology, culture, religions, let alone their military capabilities. However, we must acknowledge that their intentions are solely hostile. Alien sightings have been reported by our comrades all across the globe throughout our history (Figure 1-1). Those aliens belong to the mother ship that is lurking close to the earth orbit (Figure 1-2). We would not yet have technology to observe its presence. However, it is apparent that the destruction of the mother ship leads to the disorganisation and disintegration of the alien species belonging to it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Strategy&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game of the pool is the most sophisticated crystallization of human minds (Figure 2-1). We decided to harness its strength to defeat the aliens.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must build a giant cue that is as large as Australian continent. We shoot the cue up in the sky to hit the moon. The moon (cue ball) will first hit Mars (red ball) and pot it into the sun. The moon will bounce off and travel straight to the mother ship. Subsequently, the mother ship will be potted to the black hole (Figure 2-2). The atomisation of the mother ship through the black hole will cause a chain reaction of spontaneous combustions among the rest of aliens.
The necessity of potting the Mars can be explained as an intimidation tactic. Successful potting of the Mars will signal aliens our unity and determination.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the source of energy to propel the giant pool cue, we will harness the friction that occurs during masturbation. Friction causes heat and then heat generates energy (Figure 2-3). Human race must stop wasting their energy on masturbation. We must preserve the energy for the imminent launch of the giant cue. We will also build a nuclear power plant around Stephen Hawking’ penis that is connected to the launch button (Figure 2-4).
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a replacement for the potted moon, we will build artificial wave machines in all the major surf beaches across the globe.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Human Front Rank system&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we have declared in the opening statement, our sole purpose is to defend the human race from the impending alien attack. The Human Front treats everybody who is willing to sacrifice his life for our cause equally. We do not have ranks. We usually refer to each other, ‘Comrade’. Each member can call themself whatever they wish to, as in ‘General’, ‘Major’, ‘Corporal’ and so on if the title boosts the morale and commitment of the individual. However, those titles do not hold any practical purpose for their place in the rank.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Membership fee&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$50 dollars of joining fee or a piece of artwork. All the membership fee goes toward the after party. Artworks will be displayed at the after party for those who wish to join the party under the influence of LSD. The Human Front does not believe in banks. The money will be safely concealed at our secret location until our victory.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Closing statement&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the dawn of the human race, we have been gazing into the darkness of the endless universe and wondered if there would be any other intelligence other than us. Now, an overwhelming amount of evidence suggests that there is a hostile horde of aliens planning to take over our beautiful planet. It is high time for the human race to recognise the fact and prepare for the war. Our unity and determination can defeat the imminent alien invasion. Human race must unite against aliens.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">Opening statement</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">House Party</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/house-party" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="House Party" /><published>2020-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-30T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/house-party</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/house-party">&lt;p&gt;I kissed Sara for the first time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Eileen was in – another room&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I liked Eileen more than Sara
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Distance is – a – Tyranny&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;was the only lame excuse&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could’ve though of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at 3am in the morning
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">I kissed Sara for the first time</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nail Gun</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/nail-gun" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nail Gun" /><published>2020-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/nail-gun</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/nail-gun">&lt;p&gt;I fired a nail gun&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    into Emma’s right breast
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;click, click, click, click, click
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She bled and cried
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I held her in my arms
and gently pulled all the nails.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sincerely apologized to her
– I am sorry. I didn’t mean to hurt you
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She said – it’s ok, I will forgive you
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The holes left by the nails on her breast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;remained open and hollow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time she looks at her breast&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is reminded&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that I was the one who&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fired the nail gun at her&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;perfect breast
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">I fired a nail gun</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Planet of a Leaf</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/planet-of-a-leaf" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Planet of a Leaf" /><published>2020-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/planet-of-a-leaf</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/planet-of-a-leaf">&lt;p&gt;If the snail traced the lines of tears,
The planet of a leaf is a lush mirage.
Beneath the dirt,
The tangled cannot be untangled.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">If the snail traced the lines of tears, The planet of a leaf is a lush mirage. Beneath the dirt, The tangled cannot be untangled.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My favourite English word revised</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/my-fav-word-revised" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My favourite English word revised" /><published>2020-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/my-favourite-english-word</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/my-fav-word-revised">&lt;p&gt;tl;dr
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am revising my fav English word.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frond, it is. It’s cute.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">tl;dr</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Are you?</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/are-you" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are you?" /><published>2020-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/are-you</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/are-you">&lt;p&gt;You are happy and whole.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
But,
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Are you looking for another weirdo –
to go on adventures
to go dancing?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Someone who makes you laugh
And laughs at your jokes
Someone who makes you stand on your tippy toes
And kiss you at the right moment.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Are you?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Are you?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">You are happy and whole. But, Are you looking for another weirdo – to go on adventures to go dancing? Someone who makes you laugh And laughs at your jokes Someone who makes you stand on your tippy toes And kiss you at the right moment. Are you? Are you?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Traffic Lights</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Traffic Lights" /><published>2020-11-03T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-03T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a really good mate with Davo for a long time. Probably since just after I left school. We were the same age and hung out a lot. When we were about 30, I found out he had colour blindness. I had no idea. How would I have not known he had such a condition. There perhaps had not been the need for him to tell me. It somehow came up in the conversation and I got to know it. ‘Man, how do you read traffic lights?’ I asked. ‘Ah, that’s why traffic lights are lined up and I know when to go by the position.’ he said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in Doha for a holiday, I saw the crazy traffic lights. There are 6 of the lights and arrows everywhere around them. I took a photo of it and later asked him how he would figure out what to do with it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Just go straight, mate’ he said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">I’ve been a really good mate with Davo for a long time. Probably since just after I left school. We were the same age and hung out a lot. When we were about 30, I found out he had colour blindness. I had no idea. How would I have not known he had such a condition. There perhaps had not been the need for him to tell me. It somehow came up in the conversation and I got to know it. ‘Man, how do you read traffic lights?’ I asked. ‘Ah, that’s why traffic lights are lined up and I know when to go by the position.’ he said. When I was in Doha for a holiday, I saw the crazy traffic lights. There are 6 of the lights and arrows everywhere around them. I took a photo of it and later asked him how he would figure out what to do with it.</summary></entry></feed>