<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-03T04:50:13+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Traffic Lights</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Traffic Lights" /><published>2020-11-03T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-03T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a really good mate with Davo for a long time. Probably since just after I left school. We were the same age and hung out a lot. When we were about 30, I found out he had colour blindness. I had no idea. How would I have not known he had such a condition. There perhaps had not been the need for him to tell me. It somehow came up in the conversation and I got to know it. ‘Man, how do you read traffic lights?’ I asked. ‘Ah, that’s why traffic lights are lined up and I know when to go by the position.’ he said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in Doha for a holiday, I saw the crazy traffic lights. There are 6 of the lights and arrows everywhere around them. I took a photo of it and later asked him how he would figure out what to do with it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Just go straight, mate’ he said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">I’ve been a really good mate with Davo for a long time. Probably since just after I left school. We were the same age and hung out a lot. When we were about 30, I found out he had colour blindness. I had no idea. How would I have not known he had such a condition. There perhaps had not been the need for him to tell me. It somehow came up in the conversation and I got to know it. ‘Man, how do you read traffic lights?’ I asked. ‘Ah, that’s why traffic lights are lined up and I know when to go by the position.’ he said. When I was in Doha for a holiday, I saw the crazy traffic lights. There are 6 of the lights and arrows everywhere around them. I took a photo of it and later asked him how he would figure out what to do with it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A fake leg</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-leg" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A fake leg" /><published>2020-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-leg</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-leg">&lt;p&gt;My dad parked his car in the disabled parking spot. There were two parking inspectors, checking the cars. He grabbed a torn piece of Carlton slab box, rolled it up and inserted it into the bottom opening of the jeans on the left. He slowly got out of the car and limped toward the officers. He banged the shin of his left leg with his fist a few times. It made the noise of fist hitting a cardboard box. He smiled at the officers. ‘I parked there. It’s fake, mate. I hope it’s alright.’ 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was the lengths that he would go to in order to con people.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">My dad parked his car in the disabled parking spot. There were two parking inspectors, checking the cars. He grabbed a torn piece of Carlton slab box, rolled it up and inserted it into the bottom opening of the jeans on the left. He slowly got out of the car and limped toward the officers. He banged the shin of his left leg with his fist a few times. It made the noise of fist hitting a cardboard box. He smiled at the officers. ‘I parked there. It’s fake, mate. I hope it’s alright.’ That was the lengths that he would go to in order to con people.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My favourite English word</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/acound-the-corner" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My favourite English word" /><published>2020-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/my-favourite-english-word</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/acound-the-corner">&lt;p&gt;tl;dr
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite English word is bubble. It is magical.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">tl;dr</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Around the corner</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/acound-the-corner" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Around the corner" /><published>2020-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/around-the-corner</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/acound-the-corner">&lt;p&gt;I feel like I lost everything that matters to me. Now, every step is a struggle. Every effort seems meaningless.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But,
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s around the corner makes it worthwhile for me to keep going – even though what awaits makes me die in the most horrible way I cannot even imagine. I am hopeful that I may find something amazing once I turn the corner.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A low dose of optimism is the root of suffering. I am suffering now because I am looking forward to seeing what is around the corner. I will probably suffer more once I turn the corner. But, there is another corner to turn. I keep going to that corner again.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an existential hell. Walking down the road is horrible because I do not find any meaning to do so. Even flowers on the sidewalk make me feel sad and lonely. Yet, I still keep going because I have just enough optimism. I may find some kind of meaning once I turn the corner.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, every turn is another void. Another tolerable suffering.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">I feel like I lost everything that matters to me. Now, every step is a struggle. Every effort seems meaningless. But, What’s around the corner makes it worthwhile for me to keep going – even though what awaits makes me die in the most horrible way I cannot even imagine. I am hopeful that I may find something amazing once I turn the corner. A low dose of optimism is the root of suffering. I am suffering now because I am looking forward to seeing what is around the corner. I will probably suffer more once I turn the corner. But, there is another corner to turn. I keep going to that corner again. This is an existential hell. Walking down the road is horrible because I do not find any meaning to do so. Even flowers on the sidewalk make me feel sad and lonely. Yet, I still keep going because I have just enough optimism. I may find some kind of meaning once I turn the corner. Yet, every turn is another void. Another tolerable suffering.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A woman needs a man</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/woman-need-man" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A woman needs a man" /><published>2020-09-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/woman-need-man</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/woman-need-man">&lt;p&gt;‘We live in a society where it is normal for a father to visit his kids for a few hours per fortnight. For that privilege, he pays so much money.’ Joe said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘In this culture, women do not need to have men to have a family. For men to have a family, we need commitment from women. Men need women to have a family. When a wife decides to withdraw her commitment from a husband to have a family, he loses it. A man in this culture is disposable. We are walking and talking ATM machine for them.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The society ignores male emotional pain. The family law system and our legal system consciously denies male pain in Australia. When you go to the family court, it does not even care about the father’s pain for not being able to see children. Most of them sacrificed themselves in the labour market and fought with their skills and competency. They worked hard for the family. Women see it as oppression and leave him for what, working hard for the family. They are encouraged to do anything to fulfill themselves to make it happy.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The system is really set up for a single mother to thrive. It encourages women to break up marriage. The nuclear family to succeed is greatly reduced because of the State.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marriage game is rigged. It only becomes clearer when the separation happens.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The university teaches that women are victims. Men are oppressive. Society tells them that male drive to succeed is tyranny.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘I see. I understand your pain, man.’ I said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘But, you know what, it’s much simpler than that. She left you because you were an arsehole. Don’t intellectualise it. A woman needs a man. I have faith. There is a woman out there who needs me. I’m gonna meet her one day.’&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">‘We live in a society where it is normal for a father to visit his kids for a few hours per fortnight. For that privilege, he pays so much money.’ Joe said. ‘In this culture, women do not need to have men to have a family. For men to have a family, we need commitment from women. Men need women to have a family. When a wife decides to withdraw her commitment from a husband to have a family, he loses it. A man in this culture is disposable. We are walking and talking ATM machine for them. The society ignores male emotional pain. The family law system and our legal system consciously denies male pain in Australia. When you go to the family court, it does not even care about the father’s pain for not being able to see children. Most of them sacrificed themselves in the labour market and fought with their skills and competency. They worked hard for the family. Women see it as oppression and leave him for what, working hard for the family. They are encouraged to do anything to fulfill themselves to make it happy. The system is really set up for a single mother to thrive. It encourages women to break up marriage. The nuclear family to succeed is greatly reduced because of the State. Marriage game is rigged. It only becomes clearer when the separation happens. The university teaches that women are victims. Men are oppressive. Society tells them that male drive to succeed is tyranny.’ ‘I see. I understand your pain, man.’ I said. ‘But, you know what, it’s much simpler than that. She left you because you were an arsehole. Don’t intellectualise it. A woman needs a man. I have faith. There is a woman out there who needs me. I’m gonna meet her one day.’</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Buskers</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/buskers" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Buskers" /><published>2020-09-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/buskers</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/buskers">&lt;p&gt;‘Playing guitar would be good. You just go on the street and play guitar. Everyone will love it.’ Tom said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were talking about what to do in a post-apocalyptic world. The great electromagnetic wipeout is going to burn all the electronic systems around the world, rendering computers useless. The kind which would be brought on by an abnormal solar flare or mid-size meteor explosion in the sky. No computers, no electricity, no internet, no Netflix. Everybody must be bored. They need entertainment.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Speaking of busking, I remember when Joe told us the CommBank ATM on Smith Street had a bug and it was giving away fifty dollar notes instead of twenty. We got in his car, nine of us, and drove to the ATM. There was a huge line. Everyone was withdrawing 80 bucks and getting three fifty dollar notes. Some of them tried to do it a few times and everyone behind was getting impatient.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a guitar. So, I sat next to the ATM and sang songs. Man, those guys were giving me 50 dollar notes here and there, saying yeah you are cool. Then the police came. Everybody scattered. I had many fifty dollar notes in my pockets.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually, the bank figured out who had withdrawn money from that ATM and they all had to pay. I kept them all, though.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Hey, do you remember the old busker when we played a show in Perth.’ Quang said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘He was an old dude, very ragged. He had a few missing teeth. He was busking outside of the club where I went after the show. He had a way with music. He got everybody dancing. As they danced, money was dropping from their pockets because they danced so hard. Those drunken people teased him and left. After they left, heaps of money were left on the ground. The old guy picked them up and grinned at me like he was saying this is how to busk, man.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was good. He made everybody dance so hard. Their purse and money falling out of their pockets.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘When the apocalypse comes, we’ll go busking.’
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">‘Playing guitar would be good. You just go on the street and play guitar. Everyone will love it.’ Tom said. We were talking about what to do in a post-apocalyptic world. The great electromagnetic wipeout is going to burn all the electronic systems around the world, rendering computers useless. The kind which would be brought on by an abnormal solar flare or mid-size meteor explosion in the sky. No computers, no electricity, no internet, no Netflix. Everybody must be bored. They need entertainment. ‘Speaking of busking, I remember when Joe told us the CommBank ATM on Smith Street had a bug and it was giving away fifty dollar notes instead of twenty. We got in his car, nine of us, and drove to the ATM. There was a huge line. Everyone was withdrawing 80 bucks and getting three fifty dollar notes. Some of them tried to do it a few times and everyone behind was getting impatient. I had a guitar. So, I sat next to the ATM and sang songs. Man, those guys were giving me 50 dollar notes here and there, saying yeah you are cool. Then the police came. Everybody scattered. I had many fifty dollar notes in my pockets. Eventually, the bank figured out who had withdrawn money from that ATM and they all had to pay. I kept them all, though.’ ‘Hey, do you remember the old busker when we played a show in Perth.’ Quang said. ‘He was an old dude, very ragged. He had a few missing teeth. He was busking outside of the club where I went after the show. He had a way with music. He got everybody dancing. As they danced, money was dropping from their pockets because they danced so hard. Those drunken people teased him and left. After they left, heaps of money were left on the ground. The old guy picked them up and grinned at me like he was saying this is how to busk, man. He was good. He made everybody dance so hard. Their purse and money falling out of their pockets.’ ‘When the apocalypse comes, we’ll go busking.’</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tunnel</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tunnel" /><published>2020-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel">&lt;p&gt;     I dragged my feet into the dark tunnel. There was neither day nor night. There was no light. I simply lost my sight. Not a single speck of star beamed a ray of hope. Not a single drop of rain redeemed my dry soul.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;     In summer, it burned red-hot coals like the industrial garbage furnace. In winter, it froze everything, even my bones. Neither spring nor autumn ever came. There was neither the joy of being born nor the calamity of the last dying day.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;     So, I stopped writing poems in the tunnel of darkness. I’ve burned my words in summer. I froze and shattered them in winter. I would find neither a single dime nor rhyme in my pocket. I didn’t think I deserved either one of them, anyway.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">     I dragged my feet into the dark tunnel. There was neither day nor night. There was no light. I simply lost my sight. Not a single speck of star beamed a ray of hope. Not a single drop of rain redeemed my dry soul.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Metric</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metric" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Metric" /><published>2020-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metrics</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metric">&lt;p&gt;creating of dissatisfaction –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;is the metric –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for – customer – satisfaction
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">creating of dissatisfaction –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Faith</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Faith" /><published>2020-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith">&lt;p&gt;you have faith in everything –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
but – me –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i know&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    i don’t deserve it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    why not?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">you have faith in everything –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Manifesto</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Manifesto" /><published>2020-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto">&lt;p&gt;Word created – the – World&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words created the God –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God is a word&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I speak these Words –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am the creater of the World
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">Word created – the – World</summary></entry></feed>