<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-03T04:23:40+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My Portfolio</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Traffic Lights</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Traffic Lights" /><published>2020-11-03T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-03T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/traffic-lights">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a really good mate with Davo for a long time. Probably since just after I left school. We were the same age and hung out a lot. When we were about 30, I found out he had colour blindness. I had no idea. How would I have not known he had such a condition. There perhaps had not been the need for him to tell me. It somehow came up in the conversation and I got to know it. ‘Man, how do you read traffic lights?’ I asked. ‘Ah, that’s why traffic lights are lined up and I know when to go by the position.’ he said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was in Doha for a holiday, I saw the crazy traffic lights. There are 6 of the lights and arrows everywhere around them. I took a photo of it and later asked him how he would figure out what to do with it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Just go straight, mate’ he said.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">I’ve been a really good mate with Davo for a long time. Probably since just after I left school. We were the same age and hung out a lot. When we were about 30, I found out he had colour blindness. I had no idea. How would I have not known he had such a condition. There perhaps had not been the need for him to tell me. It somehow came up in the conversation and I got to know it. ‘Man, how do you read traffic lights?’ I asked. ‘Ah, that’s why traffic lights are lined up and I know when to go by the position.’ he said. When I was in Doha for a holiday, I saw the crazy traffic lights. There are 6 of the lights and arrows everywhere around them. I took a photo of it and later asked him how he would figure out what to do with it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A fake leg</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-leg" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A fake leg" /><published>2020-11-02T02:05:30+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-02T02:05:30+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-leg</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/short-story/fake-leg">&lt;p&gt;My dad parked his car in the disabled parking spot. There were two parking inspectors, checking the cars. He grabbed a torn piece of Carlton slab box, rolled it up and inserted it into the bottom opening of the jeans on the left. He slowly got out of the car and limped toward the officers. He banged the shin of his left leg with his fist a few times. It made the noise of fist hitting a cardboard box. He smiled at the officers. ‘I parked there. It’s fake, mate. I hope it’s alright.’ 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That was the lengths that he would go to in order to con people.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="short-story" /><summary type="html">My dad parked his car in the disabled parking spot. There were two parking inspectors, checking the cars. He grabbed a torn piece of Carlton slab box, rolled it up and inserted it into the bottom opening of the jeans on the left. He slowly got out of the car and limped toward the officers. He banged the shin of his left leg with his fist a few times. It made the noise of fist hitting a cardboard box. He smiled at the officers. ‘I parked there. It’s fake, mate. I hope it’s alright.’ That was the lengths that he would go to in order to con people.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Around the corner</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/acound-the-corner" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Around the corner" /><published>2020-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/around-the-corner</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/acound-the-corner">&lt;p&gt;I feel like I lost everything that matters to me. Now, every step is a struggle. Every effort seems meaningless.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But,
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s around the corner makes it worthwhile for me to keep going – even though what awaits makes me die in the most horrible way I cannot even imagine. I am hopeful that I may find something amazing once I turn the corner.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A low dose of optimism is the root of suffering. I am suffering now because I am looking forward to seeing what is around the corner. I will probably suffer more once I turn the corner. But, there is another corner to turn. I keep going to that corner again.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an existential hell. Walking down the road is horrible because I do not find any meaning to do so. Even flowers on the sidewalk make me feel sad and lonely. Yet, I still keep going because I have just enough optimism. I may find some kind of meaning once I turn the corner.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, every turn is another void. Another tolerable suffering.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">I feel like I lost everything that matters to me. Now, every step is a struggle. Every effort seems meaningless. But, What’s around the corner makes it worthwhile for me to keep going – even though what awaits makes me die in the most horrible way I cannot even imagine. I am hopeful that I may find something amazing once I turn the corner. A low dose of optimism is the root of suffering. I am suffering now because I am looking forward to seeing what is around the corner. I will probably suffer more once I turn the corner. But, there is another corner to turn. I keep going to that corner again. This is an existential hell. Walking down the road is horrible because I do not find any meaning to do so. Even flowers on the sidewalk make me feel sad and lonely. Yet, I still keep going because I have just enough optimism. I may find some kind of meaning once I turn the corner. Yet, every turn is another void. Another tolerable suffering.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tunnel</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tunnel" /><published>2020-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/tunnel">&lt;p&gt;     I dragged my feet into the dark tunnel. There was neither day nor night. There was no light. I simply lost my sight. Not a single speck of star beamed a ray of hope. Not a single drop of rain redeemed my dry soul.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;     In summer, it burned red-hot coals like the industrial garbage furnace. In winter, it froze everything, even my bones. Neither spring nor autumn ever came. There was neither the joy of being born nor the calamity of the last dying day.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;     So, I stopped writing poems in the tunnel of darkness. I’ve burned my words in summer. I froze and shattered them in winter. I would find neither a single dime nor rhyme in my pocket. I didn’t think I deserved either one of them, anyway.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">     I dragged my feet into the dark tunnel. There was neither day nor night. There was no light. I simply lost my sight. Not a single speck of star beamed a ray of hope. Not a single drop of rain redeemed my dry soul.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Metric</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metric" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Metric" /><published>2020-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metrics</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/metric">&lt;p&gt;creating of dissatisfaction –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;is the metric –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for – customer – satisfaction
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">creating of dissatisfaction –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Faith</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Faith" /><published>2020-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/faith">&lt;p&gt;you have faith in everything –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
but – me –
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i know&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    i don’t deserve it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;    why not?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">you have faith in everything –</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Manifesto</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Manifesto" /><published>2020-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/manifesto">&lt;p&gt;Word created – the – World&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Words created the God –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God is a word&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I speak these Words –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am the creater of the World
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">Word created – the – World</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moment of Madness</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/moment-of-madness" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moment of Madness" /><published>2020-09-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/moment-of-madness</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/moment-of-madness">&lt;p&gt;A moment of madness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m waiting for you –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No consequence – No future –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll embrace you with my arms wide open&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;with clarity – purpose – deamon – angel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of a martyr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;strapped in a ticking time bomb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at the Federation Square 3pm –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sunny Sunday afternoon
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A moment of madness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come to me – Come to me –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reasoning will be a retrospective spectacle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contemplated in a gap between your baby and womb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;where I have no part to play&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m tired of –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;justifying my will with a perfect will –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no such will anyway
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A moment of madness&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free me – Free me –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defy the law of gravity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the power of reasoning –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A healthy dose of hope –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cold stare of the 3-eyed skull&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;with 20-20-20 vision&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dope, doctor, dog, dough, doctorin&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;documentation, Dostoevsky&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burn them all
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">A moment of madness</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hero Dose</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/hero-dose" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hero Dose" /><published>2020-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/hero-dose</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/creative-writing/poetry/hero-dose">&lt;p&gt;9 grams
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 grams — Big doses
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2 grams — Small doses
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9 grams — Hero dose
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="poetry" /><summary type="html">9 grams</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Human Front Manifesto</title><link href="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/human-front-manifesto" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Human Front Manifesto" /><published>2020-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-09-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/human-front-manifesto</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://mydatahack.github.io/essay/human-front-manifesto">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Opening statement&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Human Front is a military organisation to engage in an imminent space war against hostile aliens. Our primary goal is to prevent the aliens from enslaving our minds and bodies at all costs.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description of the enemy&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have little knowledge regarding their biology, culture, religions, let alone their military capabilities. However, we must acknowledge that their intentions are solely hostile. Alien sightings have been reported by our comrades all across the globe throughout our history (Figure 1-1). Those aliens belong to the mother ship that is lurking close to the earth orbit (Figure 1-2). We would not yet have technology to observe its presence. However, it is apparent that the destruction of the mother ship leads to the disorganisation and disintegration of the alien species belonging to it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Strategy&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game of the pool is the most sophisticated crystallization of human minds (Figure 2-1). We decided to harness its strength to defeat the aliens.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must build a giant cue that is as large as Australian continent. We shoot the cue up in the sky to hit the moon. The moon (cue ball) will first hit Mars (red ball) and pot it into the sun. The moon will bounce off and travel straight to the mothership. Subsequently, the mother ship will be potted to the black hole (Figure 2-2). The atomisation of the mother ship through the black hole will cause a chain reaction of spontaneous combustions among the rest of aliens.
The necessity of potting the Mars can be explained as an intimidation tactic. Successful potting of the Mars will signal aliens our unity and determination.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the source of energy to propel the giant pool cue, we will harness the friction that occurs during masturbation. Friction causes heat and then heat generates energy (Figure 2-3). Human race must stop wasting their energy on masturbation. We must preserve the energy for the imminent launch of the giant cue. We will also build a nuclear power plant around Stephen Hawking’ penis that is connected to the launch button (Figure 2-4).
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a replacement for the potted moon, we will build artificial wave machines in all the major surf beaches across the globe.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Human Front Rank system&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we have declared in the opening statement, our sole purpose is to defend the human race from the impending alien attack. The Human Front treats everybody who is willing to sacrifice his life for our cause equally. We do not have ranks. We usually refer to each other, ‘Comrade’. Each member can call themself whatever they wish to, as in ‘General’, ‘Major’, ‘Corporal’ and so on if the title boosts the morale and commitment of the individual. However, those titles do not hold any practical purpose for their place in the rank.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Membership fee&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$50 dollars of joining fee or a piece of artwork. All the membership fee goes toward the after party. Artworks will be displayed at the after party for those who wish to join the party under the influence of LSD. The Human Front does not believe in banks. The money will be safely concealed at our secret location until our victory.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Closing statement&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the dawn of the human race, we have been gazing into the darkness of the endless universe and wondered if there would be any other intelligence other than us. Now, an overwhelming amount of evidence suggests that there is a hostile horde of aliens planning to take over our beautiful planet. It is high time for the human race to recognise the fact and prepare for the war. Our unity and determination can defeat the imminent alien invasion. Human race must unite against aliens.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="essay" /><summary type="html">Opening statement</summary></entry></feed>